A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Council on Indians, 1988-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Administrative records, 1990-2012., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Minutes and agendas, 1998-2010., 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
    - 2004 January 20. (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - HB 782, 2004. (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Events, 2003. (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Mary Wade Obituary, undated. (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - 2003 November 18. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - 2003 November 18. (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - 2003 October 21. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - 2003 August 12. (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Tribal Recognition Criteria, 2003. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - 2003 June 17. (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - 2003 June 17. (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - 2003 April 15. (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Virginia Council on Indians Conference, 2003. (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - 2003 January 21. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 2002 October 15. (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 2002 August 20. (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 2002 May 21. (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 2002 February 19. (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - 2002 January 15. (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - 1999 November 16. (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - 1999 October 19. (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - 1999 September 21. (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - 1999 August 17. (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - 1999 July 20. (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - 1999 June 15. (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 1999 April 20. (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - 1999 March 16. (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - 1999 February 16. (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - 1999 January 19. (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - 1998 December 8. (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - 1998 November 17. (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - 1998 October 21. (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - 1998 September 15. (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - 1998 August 13. (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - 1998 July 8. (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - 1998 June 18. (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - 1998 May 21. (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - 1998 April 16. (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - 1998 March 5. (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - 1998 February 12. (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - 1998 January 8. (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Series II. Planning documents, 1988-2012., Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes).
  Planning documents, 1988-2012, submitted to the Virginia Council on Indians for their comment, typically through Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act. There are archaeological reviews, 1988-2012, of historic sites that are located in or near projects undertaken by federal agencies, state agencies, and private companies. There are also subject files, 1997-2012, that include correspondence, memoranda of understanding, programmatic agreements, and other related material.
  Series II is divided into two subseries: Archeological reviews and Subject files.
  Archeological reviews are organized by the agency, corporation, or individual that requested the review. Subject files were left in original order.
  - Archaeological reviews, 1988-2012., 10 cu. ft. (10 boxes)
    Archaeological reviews, 1988-2012, of historic sites that are located in or near projects undertaken by federal agencies, state agencies, and private companies. These reviews were typically prepared in accordance with Section 106 of the National Historic Preservation Act and were submitted to the Virginia Council on Indians for their comment.
    Archeological reviews are organized alphabetically by the name of the agency, corporation, or individual that requested the review.
    - AFETA Camp Peary, 2008-2009.
      - A Phase II Archaeological Significance Evaluation of Site 44YO0270 Located at Armed Forces Experimental Training Activity Camp Peary, York County, Virginia, 2008 March. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Phase II Archaeological Significance Evaluation of Site 44YO1084 Located at Armed Forces Experimental Training Activity Camp Peary, York County, Virginia, 2008 December. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery Plan for Site 44YO1084 at Armed Forces Experimental Training Activity Camp Peary, York County, Virginia, 2009 February. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - American Electric Power, 2003-2007.
      - Report on Cultural Resources at the Smith Mountain Pumped Storage Project, 2003 October 20. (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Ethnographic Report: Traditional Cultural Properties in the Wyoming-Jackson Ferry 765 Kilovolt Transmission Line Corridor, Tazewell, Bland, Pulaski, and Wythe Counties, Virginia, 2006 April. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Results of an Archaeological Survey of High Priority Areas at Leesvile Development, Bedford, Campbell, Franklin, and Pittsylvania Counties, Virginia, 2007 February. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - APM Terminals, 2004-2005.
      - Interim Report: Archaeological Data Recovery at Site 44PM12B, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2004 October. (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Interim Report: Archaeological Data Recovery, Western Halves of Sites 44PM12 and 44PM13, APM Terminals, City of Portsmouth, Virginia, 2005 January. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Appalachian Power Company, 2004-2010.
      Proprietary information restricted for 75 years (Code of Virginia, 2.2-3705.6).
      - Restricted files, 2004-2008. (Box 7, Folders 9-21)
      - Restricted files, 2009-2010. (Box 8, Folders 1-5)
    - Battersea, 2008.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of the Battersea Villa Tract, City of Petersburg, Virginia, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Bay Environmental Consulting Services, 2007.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of DSRC Road Alignment, Chesterfield County, Virginia, 2007 July. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Columbia Gas Transmission, 1991-2009.
      - Restricted files, 1991-2009. (Box 8, Folders 8-22)
    - D.R. Horton, 2004.
      - Phase II Archaeological Significance Evaluations of Sites 44PW1516, 44PW1517, and 44PW1520, at the Proposed Villages at Rippon Lodge in Prince William County, Virginia, 2004 September. (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Treatment Plan and Research Design for Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44PW1516 and 44PW1517 at the Proposed Villages at Rippon Lodge in Prince William County, Virginia, 2004 October. (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Memorandum of Agreement Between D.R. Horton, Inc., The Virginia Department of Historic Resources and the Norfolk District, Corps of Engineers Relative to the Villages of Rippon Lodge in Prince William County, Virginia, 2004 October. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Development Consulting Services, 2006.
      - Archaeological Removal of Five Historic Burials from Site 44ST0623 at the Quantico Corporate Center Tract, Stafford County, Virginia, 2006 April 27. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Draper Aden Associates, 2008-2010.
      - Phase I Intensive Cultural Resources Survey, Dundee Wetlands Bank, Hanover County, Virginia, 2008. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Archaeological Investigations for the Exit 13 Sewer System Extension, Phase 1, Washington County, Virginia, 2010 December 30. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - East Tennessee Natural Gas Company, 2004-2010.
      - Archaeological Investigations at Sites 44WG281 and 44WY245 in Washington and Wythe Counties, Virginia, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Northeastern Tennessee Project Environmental Assessment, 2008-2010. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - East West Partners of Virginia, 2005.
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for the Proposed Patriot's Landing Development, New Kent County, Virginia, 2005 July. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - EnSafe, 2011.
      - Addendum to the Archeological Assessment of the Mid-Atlantic Broadband Cooperative Middle Mile Expansion Project #972, Amelia, Appomattox, Bedford, Buckingham, Campbell, Charlotte, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Franklin, Greensville, Halifax, Henry, Mecklenburg, Pittsylvania, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Prince George, and Sussex Counties: As well as the Cities of Bedford, Emporia, Lynchburg and Petersburg, Virginia, 2011 June. (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Addendum to the Archeological Assessment of the Mid-Atlantic Broadband Cooperative Middle Mile Expansion Project #972, Amelia, Appomattox, Bedford, Buckingham, Campbell, Charlotte, Cumberland, Dinwiddie, Franklin, Greensville, Halifax, Henry, Mecklenburg, Pittsylvania, Powhatan, Prince Edward, Prince George, and Sussex Counties: As well as the Cities of Bedford, Emporia, Lynchburg and Petersburg, Virginia, Revised, 2011 July. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Federal Aviation Administration, 2008.
      - Environmental Evaluation Form "C" (Short Environmental Assessment) for T-Hangar Development, Culpeper Regional Airport, 2008 December. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - GDS, 2008.
      - A Phase I Archaeological Survey of Site 44CS0026 and Reconnaissance Level Survey of Dover Airfield (131-5376) Within the Proposed Dover Farm Mitigation Bank, Chesapeake, Virginia, 2008 April. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Gray and Pape, 2010.
      - Final Report: A Phase I Archaeological Survey of the Proposed Elk Island Wetland Mitigation Bank, Goochland County, Virginia, 2010 June 18. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - HHHunt Communities, 2005-2007.
      - A Phase I Cultural Resources Survey of Approximately 1184 Acres of the Wilton Plantation Tract, Henrico County, Virginia, Volume I, 2005 October. (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - A Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for the Proposed Wilton Parkway, Covering Approximately 16.3, Henrico County, Virginia, 2005 October. (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Phase II Archaeological Evaluations of Sites 44HE0521, 44HE1019, 44HE1021, 44HE1026 and 44HE1033 Located within the Wilton Plantation Tract, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 March. (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - A Phase I Archaeological Survey Along Burning Tree Road, Osborne Turnpike, Warwick Park Road and Wilton Road, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 March. (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - A Phase I Cultural Resources Survey of Approximately 1,184 Acres of the Wilton Plantation Tract, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 March. (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - A Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for the Proposed Wilton Parkway, Covering Approximately 16.3 Acres, Henrico County, Virginia Addendum: A Reconnaissance Level Architectural Survey for the Proposed Wilton Parkway, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 June. (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Phase II Archaeological Evaluations of Sites 44HE0084, 44HE1015, 44HE1017, 44HE1020, 44HE1022, 44HE1024, 44HE1025, 44HE1028, 44HE1030, 44HE1031, 44HE1034, 44HE1035, 44HE1036, 44HE1037, and 44HE1038 Located within the Wilton Plantation Tract, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 November. (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Phase II Archaeological Evaluations of Sites 44HE0084, 44HE1015, 44HE1017, 44HE1020, 44HE1022, 44HE1024, 44HE1025, 44HE1028, 44HE1030, 44HE1031, 44HE1034, 44HE1035, 44HE1036, 44HE1037, and 44HE1038 Located within the Wilton Plantation Tract, Henrico County, Virginia, Volume II, 2006 November. (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - A Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for the Proposed Wilton Parkway Covering Approximately 16.3 Acres, Henrico County, Virginia Addendum: Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for Changes to the Proposed Alignment for the Proposed Wilton Parkway, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 November. (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - View Shed Analysis, Proposed Wilton on the James Development, Henrico County, Virginia, 2006 December. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Permit Support Document, Wilton on the James, Henrico County, Virginia, 2007 January. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - James River Mitigation Landbank, 2009.
      - James River Mitigation Bank Phase III Phase I Identification Survey, 2009 February 27. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kerr Environmental Services Corp., 2005.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Areas of Potential Effect at the Boy Scout Tract, James City County, Virginia, 2005 December 12. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - MACTEC Engineering and Consulting, 2010.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey of Approximately 33 Acres at the Quantico National Cemetery, 2010 September. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - John Marling, 2004.
      - Archaeological Survey: Three Areas of Potential Development at Occoneechee State Park, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, 2004 April. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Napolitano Homes, 2011.
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Survey of Nansemond River Estates Property, CIty of Suffolk, Virginia, 2011 January. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 2010.
      - Draft Environmental Assessment, Wallops Flight Facility Alternative Energy Project, 2010 March. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - National Park Service, 1988-2011.
      - An Archaeological Survey of Historic Occupation at City Point, Virginia, 1988 July. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - A Survey of the Prehistoric Occupation of City Point, Virginia, 1989 May. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Jamestown Island Interpretive Plan I/E Task 5 Report, 2001 May. (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - The Jamestown Project Draft Development Concept Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, Volume 1, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - The Jamestown Project Draft Development Concept Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, Volume 2, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - The Jamestown Project Draft Development Concept Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, Volume 3, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - The Jamestown Project Final Development Concept Plan and Environmental Impact Statement, Record of Decision, 2003. (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Visitor Center Outline Text, 2004 May. (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Construct Interpretive Facilities at Green Spring Environmental Assessment and Assessment of Effect, 2004 August 16. (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Petersburg National Battlefield City Point Unit Bluff Stabilization Project Phase I and Limited Phase II Archaeological Investigation Management Summary, 2004 September. (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Historic Jamestowne Interpretive Concept Plan Elements Draft Environmental Assessment, 2004 November. (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Appomattox Manor Repair and rehabilitation Project Phase II Archeological Testing, City Point Unit, Petersburg National Battlefield, Hopewell, Virginia, 2005 March. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Public Access and Visitor Facilities for Five Forks Environmental Assessment/Assessment of Effect, 2005 September. (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - City Point Unit Bluff Stabilization Project Phase I and Phase II Archaeological Investigation Final Report, Site 44PG102, 2006 January 15. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Stabilize Shoreline and Bluff at City Point Environmental Assessment/Assessment of Effect, 2006 January 30. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Assessment: Relocation of Battlefield Park Tour Road and Parking Area at Fort Morton Interpretive Site and other Park Road Rehabilitations, 2007 August. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Green Spring National Historic Landmark District, 2009 March 15. (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Restricted file, 2011. (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Environmental Assessment: Design and Build Two Stacked Loop Hiking and Biking Trail Systems, 2011. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - City of Newport News, 2007.
      - Identification Survey Research Plans for Proposed Wetland Mitigation Areas, King William, Hanover, and New Kent Counties, Virginia, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Northampton County, 2004.
      - Eastern Shore of Virginia Public Service Authority Wastewater System Environmental Report, 2004 December. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Malcolm Pirnie, 2009.
      - Phase II Archaeological Survey of Sites 44YO1074 and 44YO1075 Hampton Roads Sanitation District York River Treatment Plant Expansion, York County, Virginia, 2009 August. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Rivanna Water and Sewer Authority, 2011.
      - Final Historic American Engineering Record Documentation Report Ragged Mountain Reservoir Dams Complex, Albemarle County, Virginia, 2001 September. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - RK and K Engineers, 2011.
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Investigation Route 250 Bypass Interchange at McIntire Road, Charlottesville, Albemarle County, Virginia,. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Stafford Lakes Limited Partnership, 2005.
      - A Phase I Cultural Resource Within the Development Areas of the Proposed Crow's Next Development Encompassing Approximately 440 Acres, Stafford County, Virginia, 2005 October. (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - A Phase I Cultural Resource Within the Development Areas of the Proposed Crow's Next Development Encompassing Approximately 440 Acres, Stafford County, Virginia, Appendix, 2005 October. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 2009.
      - Archaeological Site Identification and Erosion Monitoring for the TVA Reservoir Operation Compliance Project: 2005-2009 Field Seasons on Portions of Blue Ridge, Chatuge, Cherokee, Fontana, Hiwassee, Norris, Nottely, Pickick, South Holston, Watauga, and Wheeler Reservoirs, 2009 June. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - TetraTech Tesora, 2011.
      - Treatment Plan for Archaeological Monitoring and Post-Review Discoveries Off-Base Water Distribution System Upgrade USCG-Tracen, Yorktown, Virginia, 2011 February. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Thompson and Litton, 2007.
      - Cultural Resources Survey Proposed Bluestone Regional Business and Technology Center, Tazewell County, Virginia, 2007 October. (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Phase II Archaeological Evaluations, Sites 44TZ0160, 44TZ0162, and 44TZ0165, Proposed Bluestone Regional Business and Technology Center, Tazewell County, Virginia, 2008 May. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Timmons Group, 2007-2011.
      - Phase I Archaeological Survey for Approximately 493 Acres at the Turner Tract, Southampton County, Virginia, 2007 February. (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Survey for Approximately 493 Acres at the Turner Tract, Southampton County, 2008 February. (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Current Condition Assessment, Proposed Industrial Access Road Corridor, Crosspointe Centre, Prince George County, Virginia, 2008 April. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Phase II Archaeological Survey of Five Sites and a Cemetery Delineation, Turner Tract, Southampton County, Virginia, 2008 December. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Phase I Cultural Resources Survey of Varina Stream Mitigation Bank, Henrico County, Virginia, 2011 September. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Troutman Sanders, 2007.
      - Cobbs Creek Reservoir: Phase II Archeological Investigations and Recordation of Historic Architectural Properties, Cumberland County, Virginia, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Uncles Neck, 2007.
      - Phase I Archaeological Testing of Two BMP Locations and Six Road Crossings at the Uncles Neck Subdivision, James City County, Virginia, 2007 November. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - United State Air Force, 2004-2009.
      - Proposed Demolition, Facility 633, Langley AFB: Technical Support Studies, 2004 July 8. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Langley Air Force Base Archaeological Survey of 406 Acres Draft Report, 2004 October. (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Langley Air Force Base Archaeological Survey of 406 Acres, 2005 February. (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Langley Air Force Base Archaeological Evaluation of 11 Sites, Draft Report, 2006 October. (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Langley Air Force Base Archaeological Evaluation of 11 Sites, 2007 March. (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Langley Air Force Based Water Treatment Plant Proposed Demolition, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - United States Army, 2007-2012.
      - Final Environmental Assessment for the Residential Communities Initiative at Fort Lee, Virginia, 2007 January. (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Final Environmental Impact Statement, Implementation of Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC) Recommendations and Other Army Actions at For Lee, Virginia, and Fort A.P. Hill, Virginia, 2007 February. (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Draft Environmental Assessment for the Proposed Infantry Platoon Battle Course, Fort A.P. Hill, Bowling Gree, Virginia, 2008 November. (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Draft Supplemental Environmental Assessment, Qualifications Training Range at Fort Lee, Virginia, 2010 February. (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Real Property Master Plan Environmental Assessment (RPMP EA), U.S. Army Garrison, Fort Lee, Virginia, 2010 March 15. (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Wealthy in Heart: Oral History of Life Before Fort A.P. Hill, 2011. (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Phase III Data Recovery Excavations at Site 44FX0223, Fairfax County, Virginia, 2012 January. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - United States Army Corps of Engineers, 1998-2011.
      - Final Report: Cultural Resource Investigations at Section 29 at Arlington House, The Robert E. Lee Memorial, Arlington County, Virginia, 1998 September. (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Archaeological Survey and Testing of Sites and Areas in Occoneechee WMA, in Island Creek WMA, at Poole's Mill, and at Stark's Mill, Halifax and Mecklenburg Counties, Virginia, and Vance County, North Carolina, Volume I, 2003 September. (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Final Report, Archaeological Investigations at the Former American Viscose Plant (Site 44RN348) and the Maher Field Site (44RN221), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2004 March. (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery at 44MC491 (Area 1): Woodland Settlement and Subsistence Practices on an Alluvial Island in the Middle Roanoke River Valley, John H. Kerr Reservoir, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, Volume I, 2004 May. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery at 44MC491 (Area 1): Woodland Settlement and Subsistence Practices on an Alluvial Island in the Middle Roanoke River Valley, John H. Kerr Reservoir, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, Volume II (Appendices I-IV), 2004 May. (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Archaeological Data Recovery at 44MC491 (Area 1): Woodland Settlement and Subsistence Practices on an Alluvial Island in the Middle Roanoke River Valley, John H. Kerr Reservoir, Mecklenburg County, Virginia, Volume III (Appendices V-X), 2004 May. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Archaeological Survey and Testing of Sites and Areas in Occoneechee WMA, in Island Creek WMA, at Poole's Mill, and at Stark's Mill, Halifax and Mecklenburg Counties, Virginia, and Vance County, North Carolina, Volume I, 2004 September. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Archaeological Survey and Testing of Sites and Areas in Occoneechee WMA, in Island Creek WMA, at Poole's Mill, and at Stark's Mill, Halifax and Mecklenburg Counties, Virginia, and Vance County, North Carolina, Volume II, 2004 September. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Historical and Architectural Documentation of the Former American Viscose Plant and Wasena Park, Roanoke, Virginia, 2005 March. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Phase II Evaluation of Sites 44HN356, 44HN357, 44HN360, and Intensive Level Architectural Evaluation of the Timberlake Farmstead, VDHR 042-203, Proposed Rutland Development Area, Hanover County, Virginia, 2005 September. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Draft Report, Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44RN2/70 (Buzzard Rock II Site) and 44RN72, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2006 October. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Draft Report, Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44RN2/70 (Buzzard Rock II Site) and 44RN72, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, Appendices, 2006 October. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Final Report, Archaeological Data Recovery at Sites 44RN2/70 (Buzzard Rock II Site) and 44RN72, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 February. (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Draft Recovery Excavations at the Sandy Site (44RN220), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 March. (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Draft Report Data Recovery Excavations at the Sandy Site (44RN220), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 March. (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Final Report Data Recovery Excavations at the Sandy Site (44RN220), City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 April. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Final Report, Additional Archaeological Investigations at the Maher Field Site (44RN221), Roanoke City Schools Maintenance and Operational Center Parking Lot, City of Roanoke, Roanoke County, Virginia, 2007 April. (Box 14, Folder 1)